There's a lot of people who just want to
talk to me cuz I have a lot of
interesting things in my head but I
I keep a lot of them in kind of tight
because they're not necessarily good.
Start with the flood. Every indigenous
culture on planet Earth has a history of
a flood. From Sumeria
to damn Indonesia to the Aborigines in
Australia to the North American Indians
to the South American. They all have the
same story of a flood. It happened. The
Younger Dryas probably about 14,000
years ago and they all have the same
cause. What was the cause of the flood
in the Bible? Uh I think it was because
God got angry with people on Earth and
decided to
uh kill them all. That's also things to
do with the Elohim and the Nephilim and
trying to cleanse the Earth from them
and that's why he saved
Noah. God didn't save Noah, Noah
believed. If you read the Bible it said
Noah
started building a boat
at a time when it had never rained on
the Earth. They'd never seen rain
before. Oh. Do you know how long it took
him?
No. 40 [__] years. Wow.
>> Imagine building a boat in the middle of
Palestine for 40 years. But Noah just
but for some reason he believed it that
whatever that was telling him was right.
Didn't matter what anyone else said.
He just listened and just kept building
his damn boat. And then one day the
unthinkable happened. It started to
rain. He had the animals in there and
everything he was supposed to and it
started to rain.
And guess what?
Everything else on Earth died who didn't
listen. Somehow
>> came because of the shitty state of
humanity. Mhm. Man had grown so wise in
his own eyes just like we are right now.
Yeah man, we're really getting close to
that point of something
like that happening, isn't it?
>> Yeah, you can feel it. I can definitely
feel it, yeah.
>> Yeah. And as there's war in the Middle
East and plagues coming out of the
ground, people cutting their [__]
dicks off.
80% of America's overweight and they
think they're doing the right thing but
they're not. Mhm. Mhm. They just believe
anything they see on a [__] screen.
The changing the weather.
Hey, look. They have IV clinics all
across America where if you drink
yourself to oblivion the night before
you can go get a IV. Oh, okay.
>> matter what you do. We'll fix it with
medicine. You can't stop shoveling food
in your mouth. We'll cut your stomach
out.
Yeah, yeah.
>> And then if that doesn't work, you gain
the weight back, we'll give you a diet
pill. Yeah, yeah. It doesn't make any
sense and
and all that is basically because
everybody is so anxious about their life
and they don't have clarity of what to
do or their purpose. So they end up
going for the comfort, right? And what's
easy.
>> They think they're here just to be
comfortable. They don't think they have
any job to do. They don't think they
serve a purpose on this Earth. They
think the Earth was put here for them.
Mhm.
>> That's humanity's problem is they think
the Earth is put here for them to just
[__] do whatever they want with it.
Put here to do something and it wasn't
just to make yourself comfortable. It
wasn't to make money. [__] we invented
money. Yeah, exactly.
>> Humanity's invented a whole [__]
world and that's all they occupy
themselves with, bro.
Think about it. Sports,
media,
music, economy, job, building,
automotive. All this is just the
imagination of man.
That's all it is and that's all they
think about. Very few people come out
here. Mhm. Mhm. And if they do, they
just come out here to take pictures of
it to show other people. They don't
actually come to enjoy it anymore.
Exactly. Exactly.
>> And that that's what I'm saying, man.
People don't live like we're designed
and that's why we're in this [__] up
state. And you can see the signs. What
happens to your body
when it gets a virus in it? Well, you
get sick. You start getting symptoms.
>> first symptom you usually feel? Getting
fever. Fever? Yeah, yeah.
>> Come. Look at planet Earth.
It's getting hot.
>> Oh. It's
>> What usually happens next? Uh You start
to shake. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Look at all the earthquakes. Then you
might throw up.
Whoa.
Look at all the tsunamis. You might
sweat. Look at the floods.
Wow, I never I never saw it that way. I
mean, I do know that the place is a
living thing as well as the other
planets and the sun and But people don't
think about that anymore, dude. All they
do is [__] They think that this was put
here to take this mountain and dig the
gold out of it so they can make a
necklace. Or let's take these rocks and
let's build a house. Let's build our
house. Why?
Because we need a place to live. Man,
you What What [__] wrong with this?
The freaking place has everything that
we need to survive here.
>> You can sweat. You're warm-blooded. You
can make your air conditioning your
heat.
All you have to do is not use the [__]
that they give you and use your [__]
God-given intelligence to pick a
suitable place on planet Earth to exist.
>> I must believe that the design that God
or whatever created us did, it's a good
design, you know, because everything
else in nature works perfectly. We lived
thousands of years without modern
medicine, right?
>> Talk about modern medicine. Yeah, I see.
>> In the greatest country on planet Earth,
America, okay.
What has our technology and our science
given us? Oh, if you don't have
insurance, we don't care. Mhm.
>> A medical billing officer decides
whether you live or die, whether the
medication they prescribe they're going
to pay for or not. And if you ain't got
the money, you can just die.
It's just another form of control. Yeah,
yeah. Definitely.
>> They create the sickness and then sell
you the [__] cure and make sure you
have insurance, too. They're going to
feed you every month. And what are they
doing? You got to think about the whole
loop. Man, they they take your life. You
spend your time and turn it into money.
And then they take your money in order
to give you your health back.
Why the [__] wouldn't you just be
healthy?
Why wouldn't you just exercise and
proper food?
Like and just live like the [__] you
were supposed to. That's that's also
basically because their mind is being
controlled but not in a way that you see
it in movies, right? Where they just
spread like this signal and everybody is
like a robot. Personal accountability.
You are responsible for your health.
Mhm.
>> Think about this. You Remember I told
you to simulated world they just made
up? Yeah, yeah. Where does your
protection come from?
Well, in the forest it comes from you.
You can look around. You better see that
snake before he sees you. Mhm.
>> Mhm. If you encounter a mountain lion,
you better damn well have something
inside of you. Mhm. Now, let's go into
the the simulated world out there.
If you have a something threatening you,
you call the police.
Mhm.
Whoa. In fact, that's all you can do.
You can't even defend yourself. If you
attack them, you go to jail. Mhm.
Somebody can sit there and say anything
he wants about you, talk about your
family, anything and you can't touch
him. You have to
hope that somebody wrote words on a
piece of paper somewhere that says it's
illegal so he can get what's coming to
him.
Dude, I [__] hate it. It makes no
sense to me. At all. At all. And And you
see people Oh, but it's more control.
Why? Well, we gave all the control to
the We gave it to them. We just gave it
to them. We elect them. They go out,
they vote. That's all they think about.
Somebody says something writes it down
on a piece of paper and 300 million
people believe it. That makes it real.
That's what a law is. Mhm. And the only
law that I really understand is the law
of the jungle.
The strong and the smart survive. The
weak and the dumb do not. Mhm. But that
has been changed. Come to America, it's
equality for all.
That means you are equal to somebody who
has spent no time training, no time
working, no time doing anything. You all
have the same existence. That has bent
reality.
It's an old old old myth from Africa.
Every day a zebra gets up and he must
outrun a lion or he will die. Yeah.
>> And every day a lion gets up and he must
outrun a zebra or he will starve. Mhm.
God made everything pretty plain to see
but nobody [__] pays attention to
what is right there.
>> [snorts]
>> It's right [__] there. It's right
[__] there, man. Totally.
>> But But But you can't. Why? Because of
the Super Bowl and because of the news.
Because all the [__] they literally
throw in front of your face cuz you have
to cut your grass. You better You got to
go to work. You got to pay all of your
power bills. You have to buy your food
from the grocery store. Hell, there's a
gas shortage in the US right now. It's
their own goddamn fault. But
But guess what? They're all How are we
going to get food? We can't transport it
to the store.
Mhm.
As if that's where food comes from. I
mean, they definitely
uh made their way to totally disconnect
us from nature. I'm sure that if people
gets to see the benefits that being in
nature brings and they actually allow
themselves to enjoy it and see it, feel
it, and connect with it,
they can understand and they can start
You can't go back.
>> Wake up. Exactly. You can't go back once
that you see it. Being awake, right? You
cannot go back to be part of that
machine
because you know that it's totally
inhuman.
And it's all you made to
enslave us and You might think I'm an
anarchist. No, I'm a naturalist. I can
definitely relate to that, too, man.
From all of these thing and
that we've been going through with the
AI and coming here to the mountain,
we came to
the idea of creating this app.
So
when you are in nature,
you can actually have a moment to just
stay still,
think about your
stuff,
think about your problems, think about
your
uh traumas and
get the clarity in the mountains and you
get the answers. Don't take your phone
with you on something like that. You go
talk to that mountain.
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
>> that mountain. You can't do
See, that's part of the problem.
Is everything is being routed through
the digital world. Mhm, mhm. And I'll
tell you
why has humanity ruled the planet for so
long?
What makes us superior to all the other
creatures?
Intelligence.
>> Our teeth?
Is it our speed or our strength?
No.
It's our intelligence and our ability to
communicate. Mhm, mhm.
Whoever has the highest intelligence
and the best communication rules planet
Earth.
Do you agree?
We agree.
Oh. And that basically connects to
Israel. Well, hold on.
Homo sapien used to have those two
things.
Now, what has it?
We've created artificial intelligence
>> which is vastly smarter to us. How do we
communicate?
With a phone.
Whoa.
Wait a minute.
We are no longer the smartest, most
communicative things on planet Earth.
Mhm. These things, and by the way, we
gave them all the information.
We gave them all the information.
>> us.
Yeah, from us.
>> put anything in, it can nothing can
happen. Yeah, yeah.
>> They take one piece of information that
you perceive as reality and they
extrapolate on it in ways that you can't
imagine. Mhm, mhm. In the same way
that your brain works different than
your dog's. Mhm.
You ever had a dog? Yeah, yeah. Did your
dog know that you owned him?
In a way, yeah. He knows that I'm the
master, right? Yeah, does he know that
you own him and control everything about
him? No, no, because he's just a an
animal. Okay, correct. He is of lower
intelligence. Yeah, yeah. When you
speak, the way you communicate, can he
understand what you're saying?
No, but he can feel it. He In a way.
>> with you, for sure. Mhm, mhm. Now,
let's say this. The computers.
Mhm.
Oh, do you know that they own you?
I don't know, but you follow Google Maps
everywhere you go. Mhm. You go online to
check your bank balance where you put
your entire life's work.
Mhm. The st- the street lights are
controlled by AI.
The electricity flowing into your home
is controlled by a computer. In fact,
everything you know, passport entry, the
water fountain, Mhm. the soap dispenser
is now run by a [__] computer.